Amirul Islam Al Mamun

Competitive Programmer & Mentor

Passionate in programming. Well experienced and skilled enough in Algorithms and Data Structure. Well educational background with good results in each phase, improving everyday by working hard. Having almost 3 years of experience in national level programming contest and some development work experience too. Highly ambitious, like to learn new things and ready for taking new challenges.



- amirulislamalmamun@gmail.com
- 66 AK Khandakar Road, Dhaka 1212, Bangladesh
- github.com/shiningflash

01521400404

- in linkedin.com/in/amirulislamalmamun
- shiningflash

WORK EXPERIENCE

Competitive Programmer & Mentor BRAC University ACM Student Chapter

02/2017 - Present

- participating in almost all NCPC and IUPC on behalf of BRAC University
- guiding junior contestant to build up their programming skills by taking various workshops and CSE Bootcamps

Contact: Shaily Roy, Lecturer, BRAC University - shaily.roy@bracu.ac.bd

Student TutorBRAC University

10/2019 - Present

Subject: Discrete Mathematics

Contact: Mirza Md. Tanjim shorif Mugdho, Lecturer, BRAC University mirza.mugdho@bracu.ac.bd

Problem Setter and Contest Moderator Toph Online Judge

12/2019 - Present

toph.co

- 16th December Programming Contest 2019
- BRACU Intra-University Programming Contest'19 etc

Contact: Mohammad Abdullah Matin Khan, Trainer, BRAC University - zarziskhan@gmail.com

PROJECT WORK

VH Online Hospital (2020)

Mobile Application (Technology: Java, XML, Firebase)

BRACU Student Tutor Management App (2020)

Mobile Application (Technology: Java, XML, Firebase)

Sorting Algorithm Visualization (2019)

Desktop Application (Technology: Java, JavaFX, FXML, Derby)

Online Voting System (2019)

Web Application (Technology: PHP, HTML, CSS, mySQL)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science BRAC University

12/2016 - Present

100% scholarship

SKILLS

Competitive Programming Problem Solving Ability

Data Structure Algorithms Mobile Application

Django Linux Git Leadership Team Work

CHARITY ORGANIZATIONS

Head of Human Resources, Voice Of Humanity (03/2020 - Present)

AWARDS

Champion at BUCC Intra-University Programming Contest (11/2017)

BRAC University

Contestant, bracu_silkRoad

2nd Runner Up at BUCC Intra-University Programming Contest (Senior) (02/2019)

BRAC University

• Team Leader & Contestant, bucc nahid

2nd Runner Up at BUCC Intra-University Programming Contest (Senior) (09/2018)

BRAC University

Team Leader & Contestant, SketchUP

8th at UITS Inter-University Programming Contest (10/2019)

National Contest

• Team Leader & Contestant, silkRoad

12th at INWED Techfest Programming Contest, IUB (06/2019)

National Contest, by IEEE Bangladesh

Team Leader & Contestant, bracu_silkRoad

24th in AUB Inter University Programming Contest (2018)

National Contest

Team Leader & Contestant, bracu_silkRoad

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE

C++ Java Python